

Nikiforos Karamitros

Full Stack Developer

■ nickiforoskaramitros@gmail.com **J** 6947527925 • Athens, Greece

Experience

Junior Full Stack Dev Jul 2023 - Present

Chemical Safety Software

Sales Representative Aug 2022 - Jan 2023

Plaisio Computers, Peristeri GR

Education

Oct 2021 - Jun 2023 Software Engineer

AKMI INTERNATIONAL, Athens GR

Web Designer / Game Developer Oct 2021 - Oct 2022

AKMI INTERNATIONAL, Athens GR

Certificates

The Complete SQL Cource 2024 - SQL Apr 2024

Server Udemy

Game Design 101 - 301 Mar 2023

AKMI INTERNATIONAL

Jan 2023 **Arduino Programming And App**

Development

AKMI INTERNATIONAL

Jan 2023 PC Troubleshooting And Repair

AKMI INTERNATIONAL

About Me

I am a passionate Full Stack Developer, with a strong background in a similar position. I am well versed in developing in the .NET Framework, and using languages like C, C++, C# and VB. I also have an advanced understanding of SQL (MySQL and especially MSSQL) as well as knowledge in Database Design. I've used Python, Java and Javascript (backend with Node.JS) for different personal projects, such as discord bots and desktop apps. I am very comfortable with the Unity Game Engine (and C#) with experience both in desktop games as well as mobile. Lastly, I've used HTML/CSS/JS to create websites, either for academic purposes or personal purpose.

Being a Technology based Sales Representative at Plaisio

Personal details

Website nickkay.com

Github:

github.com/NickKay0

Skills

MSSQL / MYSQL / SQL

.NET Development (C,C#,C++)

Unity Game Engine

Excel / Word / Powerpoint

HTML / CSS / JS

Python

Java

Languages

Greek

English

Hobbies

- Programming, Coding And App Development
- Playing & Developing Games

Computers, as well as having a huge interest in keeping up with new technologies, I have both a broad and deep understanding of hardware in the PC and Networking space.

My ambition is learning and understanding as much as I possibly can with every aspect of technology, whether it's hardware, software and everything in-between.

- Digital And Pixel Art
- PC Building And Upgrading